go go go go let's go sh
上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上上
it false
假 假
advertising and
广告和广告广告
drink you can't stop drinking it the
和广告 喝酒,你无法停止 喝它
喝酒,你无法停止 喝它,
drink you can't stop drinking it the
more you drink the healthier you'll be
喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝越喝越健康
喝得越多 越健康,你就会更健康
more you drink the healthier you'll be
wow it looks so yummy let's buy some
喝多喝多喝多喝越健康,你就会好哇 看起来很好吃,我们买点
哇,看起来好好吃呀,我们买点吧
wow it looks so yummy let's buy some
okay
哇,看起来好好吃,我们买点好点的吧
1 2
1 2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2
3 wow it's so
3 哇,这样
yummy it's empty I want some
3哇,好好吃,空空,我要来点
more let's buy more this
买多买多买多买多买多买多买多买
time
时间
wow
哇哇哇哇
watch
观察观察
out Danger let's go
出去危险,我们走吧
ha that was really close what happened
哈哈真的很接近 发生了什么事
to you we just had this
发生在你身上的事 我们刚刚有了这个
对你,我们刚刚有了这个
to you we just had this
drink we couldn't stop drinking him and
我们刚喝了这杯酒 不停地喝着他
我们不停地喝他 喝他
drink we couldn't stop drinking him and
this is what happened to
喝着喝着喝着我们不停的喝着他 这就是发生在
这就是发生在
this is what happened to
us I need I stop
и и惠璶и и惠璶и и璶氨ㄓ
drinking something's wrong let's go have
иии惠璶иぃ耻皊 иǐ
喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝
drinking something's wrong let's go have
a
喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝喝
a a/
a
look I'll go
一看一看一看我就去
I'll go buy one excuse
我去买一个借口
me I lost my
我失去了我,我失去了我
shoe police thank you for your
我失去了我的鞋警,谢谢你
鞋警察谢谢你
shoe police thank you for your
cooperation papion check the drink
合作检查饮料
okay
还好
yes oh it smells
是的,哦闻闻闻
great I'm going to take a sip stop
是的,哦,闻起来好香 好香,我要去 喝一小口
太好了,我要去 喝一小口停止
great I'm going to take a sip stop
something's wrong with the
好极了,我要去喝一口 停止有问题的东西与
drink look it contains a lot of
饮酒,看起来里面有很多
unhealthy stuff they might make your
饮酒,看起来里面有很多不健康的东西 他们可能会做你
健康不健康的东西 他们可能会成为你
unhealthy stuff they might make your
hair fall out or make you
不健康的东西 他们可能会让你的头发掉掉出来 或者让你变成
floated everyone stop drinking it who
所有人都停止喝它,谁
made this drink it's horrible don't
所有人都停止喝水 谁做的这杯酒 太可怕了
喝了这杯酒 太可怕了,不要
made this drink it's horrible don't
worry there's no case that I can't
喝了这杯酒 太可怕了 不要担心没有案子我不能办
担心没有案子我办不到
worry there's no case that I can't
solve with my special ingredients people
用我特别的素材来解答问题
won't stop drinking
用我的特殊原料解决问题 人们不会停止喝酒
不停饮酒
won't stop drinking
it as long as I can make money I don't
只要我能挣钱,我就不停止喝酒
只要我能挣钱,我不会
it as long as I can make money I don't
care if you lose your hair or become
只要我能挣钱 我不管你有没有头发
bloated
膨胀
the police is coming I need to
警察来了,我需要
hide it says the factory that makes the
上面写着 制造工厂的工厂
drink is here it's in such a remote
上面说制造饮料的工厂就在这里 就在这么远的地方
酒在这里,在如此遥远的地方
drink is here it's in such a remote
place let's go in
酒就在这里,在这么偏僻的地方 我们进去吧
now huh H nobody's here let's search
哈哈哈哈哈哈,这里没有人,我们找找看
around okay
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈没有人在这里,让我们四处找找找找找,好吗?
okay that's strange where are they
好奇怪他们在哪里
hiding huh what are these strange
奇怪他们藏在哪里啊? 这些怪异的是什么?
隐藏着这些奇怪的东西
hiding huh what are these strange
things ouch that
隐藏着这些奇怪的东西
触摸事物
things ouch that
hurts you
伤害你的触摸
an stop right
右停停
there
此处
keep playing guys I'm going to leave
继续打球,我要走了
you'll never catch Dr
继续打球,我要走了,你永远抓不到博士
你永远抓不到博士
you'll never catch Dr
antel
你永远抓不到Antel医生
英特尔
antel
huh you can't run
英特尔,你跑不跑不跑啊
away I don't want to
我不想离开,我不想离开
drink
饮
help my hair you're coming with us to
帮助我的头发 你和我们一起去
the police
帮我把头发弄好 你跟我们一起去报警
station Sheriff labor safety
劳动安全警长站
talk kids some advertisements might
和孩子聊天,一些广告可能
trick us into buying their products
有些广告会骗我们买他们的产品
骗我们买他们的产品
trick us into buying their products
don't believe everything they say and be
骗我们去买他们的产品 不相信他们所说的一切
不要相信他们所说的一切
don't believe everything they say and be
careful not to be fooled please remember
不要相信他们所说的一切 并且小心不要被愚弄 请记住
千万不要被愚弄,请记住
careful not to be fooled please remember
that
,该数额,
dangerous
危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,危险,
friends we got stop right
朋友,我们有 停下来右右
there hey follow
喂喂喂喂喂喂 喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂 喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂 喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂喂
me oh
哦,哦,我哦
no bye-bye you bad thieves
你们这些坏贼,再也不能拜拜了
go oh huh Mr bear what's going on
哦 熊先生 发生什么事了?
熊先生,这是怎么回事
go oh huh Mr bear what's going on
Sheriff lavador some kids have been
哦,走吧,熊先生... ... ......
警长 厕所 警长 一些孩子已经
Sheriff lavador some kids have been
stealing candy from my shop help me
警长,马歇尔道夫 有一些孩子偷糖果 从我的店里偷 从我店里的糖果,帮助我
从我店里偷糖果来帮我
stealing candy from my shop help me
please
偷我店里的糖果 帮我一下
请
please
huh don't worry leave it to
不要担心,让给
us how much did you
我们之间你做了多少
get seriously is this all you
说正经的是你
got
说真的,你只有这些了
已经拥有
got
shall we go back for more Mr bear knows
我们要回去找更多的熊先生知道
我们回去找更多的熊先生知道
shall we go back for more Mr bear knows
who we are now we can't then what should
我们应该回去找更多的熊先生 知道我们现在是谁
现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,
who we are now we can't then what should
we
现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,现在的我们,
我们
we
do we need to find someone to help us
我们需要找人来帮助我们
that's my
我们需要找人来帮助我们 这是我的
toy
玩具
minutes I think I found
玩具分钟,我想我发现
one hey give it back to Little
把它还给小小
Koala okay
把它还给小Koala,好吗?
toy wow
玩具哇哇
thanks little why don't we be friends
少谢少谢少谢 不如我们做朋友吧
friends yes if we are when someone takes
何不我们做朋友? 是的,如果我们是 当有人带走
朋友是的,如果我们是 当有人采取
friends yes if we are when someone takes
away your toy we can protect you sounds
如果有人拿走你的玩具 我们就能保护你的声音
把你的玩具拿走 我们可以保护你的声音
away your toy we can protect you sounds
great I'll be safe
把你玩具带走,我们保护你 听起来不错,我会很安全
太好了,我会安全
great I'll be safe
then from now on friend
太好了,我以后就安全了 以后交朋友
从此以后,我以朋友的情友盟誓,
then from now on friend
come on friend let's go have some fun
从此以后 朋友 朋友 朋友 咱们去玩玩吧
来,朋友,我们去玩玩吧
come on friend let's go have some fun
uhhuh by the way can you pretend to have
顺便说一句,你能假装有
a stomach ache a stomach ache like
顺便说一句 你能假装肚子痛吗?
胃痛 肚子痛 就像
a stomach ache a stomach ache like
this wow you did it so
哇,你这样做了
well when you see Mr bear in the shop
当你在店里看到熊先生的时候
keep acting like you have a stomach ache
当你看到熊先生在店里 一直表现得好像肚子痛似的
表现得好像肚子疼似的
keep acting like you have a stomach ache
why to fool him of course no no no we're
表现得好像你肚子疼 为什么要骗他 当然不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,
为什么愚弄他 当然不不不不不不我们
why to fool him of course no no no we're
going to play a game huh we're friends
为什么要骗他 当然,当然,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,我们是要玩一个游戏 呵呵,我们是朋友
玩游戏啊,我们是朋友嘛
going to play a game huh we're friends
we won't lie to you come on go
来玩个游戏吧,我们是朋友,我们不会骗你
inside
内
wow Doby watch out someone's coming
哇,多比,小心,有人来了
in leave it to
哇,多比,小心,有人来 来,让它
留待
in leave it to
me hi kid feel free to look around
交给我 小子 随便四处看看吧
嗨,孩子,你可以随便看看周围
me hi kid feel free to look around
didn't choose what you
嗨,我孩子可以随便四处看看 没有选择你什么
你没有选择什么
didn't choose what you
want ow
没有选择你想要什么
需要wow
want ow
ow it
# 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱 爱
hurts are you all
你们是不是都受伤了
right they fell for
被他们所归依的人,
it hurry
它快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快快
hurry
快点
hurt my
快点伤伤我
伤害我
hurt my
tummy I'll take you to the hospital oh
我肚子疼,我带你去医院
我送你去医院
tummy I'll take you to the hospital oh
no I don't want to go don't worry it's
我送你去医院 哦不,我不想去,别担心
不,我不想去 不要担心,这是
no I don't want to go don't worry it's
okay no I will
不,不,我不想去 别担心,没关系,没关系,不,我会的
go what's that
开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开什么开
sound hey what are you doing
声音嘿嘿嘿你在做什么
here something
嘿,你在这里做什么
wrong I don't want to go huh is that a
错了,我不想去,哈哈哈 那是
new game
我不想去,我错了,我不想去,哈哈 是新游戏,新游戏
what they stole the
他们所偷取的,
candy let's
他们偷走的糖果,让我们
糖果,让我们
candy let's
go Yay good job Little Koala you helped
糖果,让我们去糖果 我们走吧,耶,干得好,干得好 小科阿拉你帮助
干得好,你帮了小考拉
go Yay good job Little Koala you helped
us steal a lot of candy what you stole
小Koala 你帮我们偷了很多糖果 你偷的糖果
我们偷了很多糖果 你偷的糖果
us steal a lot of candy what you stole
candy stop right
我们偷了很多糖果 你偷的糖果 停止右
there
此处
hey stealing things is against the law
偷东西是违法的
you can't run away
偷东西是违法的,你跑不掉的
你跑不掉的,你跑不掉的
you can't run away
stole the candy we have nothing to do
你跑不掉的 偷的糖果,我们什么也做不了
偷的糖果,我们什么也做不了
stole the candy we have nothing to do
with it it's not me watch
偷的糖果,我们没有 做与它无关 它不是我看
与它在一起,它不是我看着
with it it's not me watch
out is
与它在一起,它不是我 注意是
me stop right
我右站右站右站右站右站
there you're coming with us we will
你和我们一起到那里去 我们会的
never steal
你和我们一起到那里去 我们永远不会偷东西
从未偷
never steal
again and I'll never make best friends
再也不偷东西,我再也不会交到好朋友
我再也不会交到好朋友
again and I'll never make best friends
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids be careful when you make
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们在做的时候要小心
说闲话的小孩做时要小心
talk kids be careful when you make
friends you should never make friends
交朋友时要小心,不要交朋友
朋友不应该交朋友 朋友不应该交朋友
friends you should never make friends
with bad people bad friends might teach
朋友你不应该和坏人交朋友 坏朋友会教的
和坏人在一起 坏朋友会教坏人
with bad people bad friends might teach
you bad habits use bad words or do bad
坏人和坏人在一起 坏朋友会教你坏习惯 说坏话或做坏事
坏习惯是说坏话还是做坏事
you bad habits use bad words or do bad
things if your friend asks you to do
你那些坏习惯用坏话 或者做坏事 如果你朋友叫你做
如果你朋友要你做的话
things if your friend asks you to do
something bad please say no and tell
如果你朋友要你做坏事 请说不,说不
坏东西,请说不,说不
something bad please say no and tell
adults such as your teacher parents or a
坏的东西 请说不 告诉大人,比如你的老师父母或
成人,例如你的老师父母或
adults such as your teacher parents or a
police officer please remember
成人,例如你的老师父母或警官,请记住
警官,请记住
police officer please remember
that the ghost
那个鬼魂
motorbike green
绿色摩托车
light stop at Red go at
红灯车绿灯停停 红灯停 红灯停 红灯停
Green
绿绿色
huh what's that there's no one driving
那为什么没人开车?
it ah
那为什么没人驾驶它啊
ow W hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador I got hit by a ghost motorbike
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 我被一辆鬼摩托车击中
拉布拉多 我被一辆幽灵摩托车击中
Labrador I got hit by a ghost motorbike
when I crossed the street just now what
拉布拉多拉布拉多 我被一辆幽灵摩托车撞了 当我过马路时
当我刚刚过马路的时候...
when I crossed the street just now what
a ghost motorbike we'll be right
当我刚刚穿过街过马路时 一辆幽灵摩托车会怎么样?
一辆鬼魂摩托车,我们会是正确的
a ghost motorbike we'll be right
there
此处
huh where is
(a) 国家、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、地区、
he I'm
他,我,我,
here that was
在这里,这是
close we're lucky to have hard
幸好我们很努力
scales Mr
幸好我们有硬秤
平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平
scales Mr
Pangolin you called the police right oh
潘戈林先生 你叫警察对吗?
潘戈林 你报警了哦
Pangolin you called the police right oh
yes I got hit by a motorbike running a
潘戈林,你叫警察对吗 哦,是的,我被一辆摩托车撞了
是的 我被一辆摩托车撞了 开着一辆
yes I got hit by a motorbike running a
red light and you know what there was no
我被一辆开着红灯的摩托车撞了 你知道没有
红红灯,你知道什么是没有的
red light and you know what there was no
driver it's must have been a ghost
红红灯,你知道什么是没有司机的 一定是鬼魂
司机一定是鬼魂
driver it's must have been a ghost
motorbike I'm so
司机一定是一辆鬼魂摩托车
摩托车 我是如此
motorbike I'm so
scared a ghost motorbike I'm sure
摩托车 我好害怕 鬼魂摩托车 我敢肯定
吓吓鬼魂摩托车 我敢肯定
scared a ghost motorbike I'm sure
something's wrong here don't worry
被吓吓的鬼魂摩托车 我敢肯定这里出事了 不用担心
这里有些不对劲,别担心
something's wrong here don't worry
there's no case that I can't
这里有些不对劲,别担心 没有案子我办不到
solve now let's find the motorbike first
现在我们先找到摩托车吧
got
现在让我们先找到那辆摩托车
it every vehicle leaves a mark when it
每辆车都留下标记 当它
passes
每辆车经过时都留下印记
通行证
passes
by
至
it's a
由它是一个
是一个
it's a
puddle
这是一个水坑
H these are cars tire
这些是汽车轮胎
tracks and these are motorbikes tire
这些是汽车轮胎的车轨,这些是摩托车轮胎
这些脚印是摩托车轮胎轮胎
tracks and these are motorbikes tire
tracks I found the clue it must have
这些是摩托车的轮胎的车轨 我找到了它一定有的线索
我找到了它一定有的线索
tracks I found the clue it must have
gone this
我找到了线索 一定是线索
把这个拿走了
gone this
way
往这边走
方形
way
woof let's
来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,
让我们
woof let's
go
上去
look over
向下看一看
there it can't be is it a real ghost
那里不可能是真正的鬼魂吗?
there's no such thing as a
在那里不可能是它是一个真正的鬼魂 没有这样的东西像一个
没有任何东西像
there's no such thing as a
ghost there into the alley hurry up
鬼魂在巷子里,快快点
oh huh oh no it won't go
哦,哦,不,它不会去
far
远远
police Mr Turtle can you help us follow
警察,海龟先生 你能帮我们跟着吗?
the motor like over
警察,海龟先生,你能帮我们 跟着马达,像过去一样
汽车像过去一样
the motor like over
there
像那边那样的马达
此处
there
Sure hold
稳住
on Mr Turtle are you sure you can catch
乌龟先生,你真能抓得住吗?
it of
乌龟先生,你确定你能抓到它吗?
年三月一日,
it of
course
课程课程
go let's
航程走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走
go my bottom really hurts huh where are
我的底部真的很痛啊,啊,在哪里啊
we
我的底部真的很痛啊 我们在哪里?
huh the ghost motorbike
鬼魂摩托车
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
stop
hhn 停止( 停止)
停止停止
stop
huh it's a
应该是,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,是的,
com watch
是个监视器
out
外出
no I was really scared
没有,我真的很害怕
chameleon you broke the traffic rules
我真的害怕变色龙 你违反交通规则
你违反了交通规则
chameleon you broke the traffic rules
you're under
你违反交通规则 违反交通规则
下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,
you're under
arrest Sheriff labrador's safety
逮捕拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids TR traffic lights are the
儿童聊天 TR 交通灯是
signals to control traffic the red light
儿童聊天 TR 交通灯是控制红灯的信号
控制红灯的信号
signals to control traffic the red light
means
控制红光信号 以控制红光信号
中指
means
stop the green light means
意味着停止绿光意味着停止绿光
停止绿光意味着
stop the green light means
go and the yellow light means be careful
停止绿光意味着离开 黄光意味着要小心
黄光照着黄光走,要小心
go and the yellow light means be careful
whether you're a driver or a pedestrian
黄色光亮意味着要小心,无论你是司机还是行人
无论是司机还是行人
whether you're a driver or a pedestrian
you should always follow the traffic
无论你是司机还是行人,你都应该一直跟着交通
您应该始终跟踪交通流量
you should always follow the traffic
lights if you don't you might get in a
如果你没有,你应该一直跟着 交通灯,如果你没有,你可能会得到一个
灯光,如果你不,你可能会得到
lights if you don't you might get in a
traffic accident please keep that in
灯光,如果你不,你会 发生交通事故 交通事故 请保持在
交通事故 请保留在
traffic accident please keep that in
mind missing little
略微缺少心智
chicky I can't hold it anymore
想念小小小妞,我再也忍不住了
wow brother I want some ice
哇哥,我要冰块
cream just wait a few
奶油 等一等
minutes all
所有分钟
right ice cream ice cream I'll eat some
几分钟所有的权利 冰淇淋冰淇淋 冰淇淋 我吃一些
右右冰淇淋冰淇淋冰淇淋 我要吃一些
right ice cream ice cream I'll eat some
ice
冰淇淋冰淇淋冰淇淋 我吃冰淇淋
cream hey little friend
嗨,小朋友
I know a really nice ice cream shop H I
小朋友 我知道一个很棒的冰淇淋店 HI
我知道一个很棒的冰淇淋店
I know a really nice ice cream shop H I
can take you
我知道一个很棒的冰淇淋店 我可以带你去
可以带你们去
can take you
there um but I don't know who you are
可以带你去那里吗 嗯 但我不知道你是谁
在那里,嗯,但我不知道你是谁
there um but I don't know who you are
I'm not going with
在那里,嗯,但我不知道你是谁 我不跟你去
我不会跟你去的
I'm not going with
you come on I'm a friend of your parents
我不会和你一起去的,来吧 我是你父母的朋友
你过来,我是你父母的朋友
you come on I'm a friend of your parents
don't you remember that I cuddled you
我是你的父母的朋友 你不记得我抱过你吗?
你不记得我拥抱你了吗?
don't you remember that I cuddled you
when you were a baby
你不记得你小时候我抱过你吗?
当你还是婴儿时
when you were a baby
a come on hurry up or the ice cream will
当你还是婴儿时 来快快来 不然冰淇淋会
来,快点,不然冰淇淋会
a come on hurry up or the ice cream will
be all sold
来,快点,不然冰淇淋就全卖光了
out now let's go buy some ice
现在出去买冰,我们去买冰吧
cream my
现在出去,我们去买冰淇淋吧
奶油 我的奶油
cream my
brother where is
我弟弟的奶油,哪里是
he hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador my little brother is
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 我弟弟
拉布拉多 我弟弟是
Labrador my little brother is
missing what should I do don't worry
拉布拉多 我弟弟错过了 我该担心什么
少了什么我应该做什么 不要担心
missing what should I do don't worry
little kid we'll be right
少了我该做什么 不用担心孩子 我们会是对的
小孩,我们做对了
little kid we'll be right
there
此处
Sheriff Labrador just now I went to the
拉布拉多警长 刚才我去了
restroom but when I came out my little
刚才拉布拉多警长 刚才我去洗手间 但当我出来时
洗手间,但当我出来时
restroom but when I came out my little
brother was gone please find my little
但当我出来的时候 我的弟弟走了 请帮我找到我的小弟弟
哥哥走了,请找到我的小弟弟
brother was gone please find my little
brother don't worry kid there's no case
哥哥走了,请找到我的小弟弟 不用担心,孩子,没有案子
哥哥,别担心,孩子,没有案子
brother don't worry kid there's no case
that I can't
哥哥,别担心,孩子,没有案子我不能办
我无法
that I can't
solve little
我解决不了小问题
小解解解小解
solve little
CH that's my my little brother's toy
CH,那是我的小弟弟的玩具
then he must be around here let's keep
那是我弟弟的玩具,他一定在附近 我们继续吧
searching that man looks suspicious he
搜那人看起来可疑
keeps looking around he must be hiding
找寻疑似疑似疑疑的人 不断四处找寻 一定藏起来了
他一定躲起来了
keeps looking around he must be hiding
little chicky
他一定藏着小小妞
小小小鸡鸡
little chicky
somewhere stop right
小小小鸡小鸡 某处停止右
there
此处
what it's not little
是什么不小,什么不小
Chicky what are you talking about look
不是小奇奇 你在说什么 看着
奇奇,你在说什么 看什么看
Chicky what are you talking about look
it's my
奇奇你在说什么 看起来像是我的
# 这是我的 # # 这是我的 # # It's my # # It's my # #
it's my
hump you could have just said it nicely
你本可以好好地说
why did you rip my clothes I'm sorry I'm
你本可以好好说 为什么要撕我的衣服 对不起
你为何撕我衣服? 对不起
why did you rip my clothes I'm sorry I'm
so
你为什么撕我衣服? 对不起,我...
so so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so,
so
sorry Mr Camel have you seen a little
对不起 骆驼先生 你见过一点
chick who has a chubby face and is
对不起 骆驼先生 你见过一个小妞 长着胖胖的脸
长着胖胖胖脸的妞
chick who has a chubby face and is
wearing a plaid cap
长着胖胖胖脸脸 戴长盖盖帽的小妞
身戴格斗帽的人,
wearing a plaid cap
H well
戴盖盖盖盖盖帽 H很好
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
H well
ah yes I have he was with a red fox and
他和一只红狐狸在一起
是的,我有他和一只红狐狸在一起
ah yes I have he was with a red fox and
he went into the forest that's not good
啊,是的,我有他和一只红狐狸在一起, 他去了森林,这是不好的
他走进了森林,那不妙
he went into the forest that's not good
the red fox might be a kidnapper we need
红狐狸可能是我们要找的绑匪
红狐狸可能是绑匪 我们需要
the red fox might be a kidnapper we need
to find
红狐狸可能是绑匪 我们需要找到
要找到
to find
him huh there are three roads which way
他有三条路要走
do you think it is
他有三条路,你以为是这条路吗?
你认为是的吗?
do you think it is
it's all muddy here so they must have
这里很泥泥,所以他们一定有
left some Footprints let's look for
这里很泥泥,所以他们一定留了脚印 我们找找看
留下一些脚印,让我们找找
left some Footprints let's look for
their
留下一些脚印,让我们找找
他们的
their
footprints found them these are red box
这些是红色的盒子
and little chick Footprints they went
这些是红盒和小小鸡脚印 它们去的脚印
和小小小鸡脚印 他们去了
and little chick Footprints they went
this way let's
和小小妞脚印 他们往这边走,让我们
go we're going too far to the shop I
走了,我们走得太远了 到商店I
don't want to eat ice cream anymore I
我们要去的太远了 商店我不想再吃冰淇淋了
我不想再吃冰淇淋了
don't want to eat ice cream anymore I
want to go home
我不想再吃冰淇淋了 我想回家
home home no you can't go
家家 家家家 家家家家家家家家家 家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家 家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家家
home somebody help
家家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 不 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家 家
me
我,我,我
please Sheriff
警长,拜托我
Labrador
拉布拉多
nobody can run away from
拉布拉多 没有人能逃离
没有人能逃避
nobody can run away from
me take him to the police
没有人能从我身边逃跑 带他去报警
station Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids when you go out don't wander
外出时说闲话的小孩,别乱跑
off alone or take things from
外出时说话的小孩 不要一个人乱跑或拿走东西
或独自离开,或拿东西离开,
off alone or take things from
strangers if they say they'll take you
独自离开 或从陌生人那里拿东西 如果他们说会带你去
陌生人,如果他们说会带你去
strangers if they say they'll take you
home you must say
如果陌生人说他们会带你回家 你必须说
在家你必须说
home you must say
no and if they threaten you never
你们必须说不,如果他们威胁你们,你们绝不要说不;
如果他们不威胁你,那末,他们绝不警告你;
no and if they threaten you never
hesitate to shout and ask other people
如果他们警告你,你绝不犹豫,你应当喊叫,你应当问别的民众;
犹豫不决地喊叫和问别人
hesitate to shout and ask other people
around you for
犹豫不决地大声喊叫,并且向周围的人要求,
环绕在你身边
around you for
help remember these
环绕在你们周围寻求帮助,以便你们记念这些
tips no littering no
不丢垃圾提示
mosquitoes
蚊蚊子
sh go
蚊子和蚊子离开
away so many
许许许多多的
mosquitoes help stop following
这么多蚊虫 帮助停止跟随
me oh no so many mosquitoes
哦,没有这么多蚊子
run what's going
运行正在运行的运行
on my head my lips my neck that's so
跑什么跑什么 在我的头上 在我的嘴唇 我的脖子
itchy what happened to you Sheriff
警长,你发生什么事了,好痒痒啊
labador mosquitoes are everywhere in
不知你身上发生的事 到处是蚊子
蚊子无处不在
labador mosquitoes are everywhere in
town it's so scary look at what they did
镇上到处都是蚊子 看着他们做了什么太吓人了
镇镇太吓人了 看看他们做了什么
town it's so scary look at what they did
to us please help
镇镇太吓人了 看看他们对我们做了什么 请帮帮忙
请救救我们
to us please help
us they're
救救我们,救救我们,救救他们
coming Doby let's go take a
杜比,我们去吃一个
look got
杜比,我们去看看
看了看 看了看
look got
it now they can't fight me Doby hurry up
现在他们打不过我了 多比,快点
okay
还好
more and more mosquitoes are coming
蚊子越来越多,蚊子也越来越多,
looks like their breeding ground is over
越来越多的蚊子来了 好像他们的繁殖地已经结束了
看起来像他们的繁殖地 已经结束了
looks like their breeding ground is over
there oh let me check it
看起来他们的繁殖地在那边 哦 让我检查一下
out you can't fight
出不来,打不出来
me my bottom ow my face help there are
我的屁股,我的屁股,我的脸上 帮助我的脸有
too many of them let's
我的屁股,我的屁股,我的脸 帮助我的脸 有太多 他们太多,让我们
他们中太多人了,让我们
too many of them let's
go they're
他们太多,我们走吧,他们
coming hide in the
隐藏在
Box oh that's so scary there are too
盒子哦,那太吓人了,有太可怕了
many of them what should we do papion
盒子哦,那太吓人了 太多人了,我们该怎么处理Papion
许多人中,有许多人中,有许多人中,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,
many of them what should we do papion
we're surrounded by mosquitoes we need
我们该做什么? 我们被蚊虫包围 我们需要的蚊虫。
我们周围都是蚊子 我们需要的蚊子
we're surrounded by mosquitoes we need
your help mosquitoes leave it to
我们被蚊子包围 我们需要你的帮助 蚊子离开它
帮助蚊子
your help mosquitoes leave it to
me Poppy always pass
你帮蚊子的帮助留给我 罂粟总是会通过
罂粟总是通过
me Poppy always pass
away happy
快乐快乐
H wow papon why aren't they coming after
为什么他们不来找我们呢?
you because I'm wearing mosquito patches
为什么他们不来抓你 因为我戴了蚊子补丁
因为你因为我穿着蚊子贴
you because I'm wearing mosquito patches
and
因为你因为我穿着 蚊子补丁和
和
and
bracelets here you
手镯和手镯,
手镯在这里您
bracelets here you
go now they can't get close to me
走了,他们不能靠近我
hey look over there the mosquitoes are
他们现在走了 他们离我太近了 嘿 看看那边的蚊子们
嘿,看那边 蚊子是
hey look over there the mosquitoes are
coming from
看那边 蚊子从那边来
发自
coming from
there ew it
从那里起出,
在那里缝织着它
there ew it
stinks mosquitoes are still breeding
臭臭蚊子还在繁殖
they are most likely to breed in dirty
臭臭的蚊子仍然在繁殖 他们最有可能在肮脏中繁殖
他们最可能繁殖在肮脏的
they are most likely to breed in dirty
and wet places like
它们最可能繁殖在肮脏和湿湿的地方,如:
湿湿的地方如
and wet places like
this no wonder there are so many
像这样的湿湿的地方 难怪有这么多人
难怪这么多人
this no wonder there are so many
mosquitoes in this
难怪这里有这么多蚊子
里面有蚊子
mosquitoes in this
town who on earth made this
这个城市的蚊子们,在大地上造化了这个城市的蚊子们,
大地上的居民,创造了这个城市,
town who on earth made this
mess
乱成一团
hey I'm not scared of
嘿,我不怕
you bounce
你弹跳
what's going on let's
这是怎么回事,让我们
go
发生什么事了,我们走吧
上去
go
huh ouch
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
ouch
触摸( A)
help let's
来来来来来来来来 来来来来来来
go
上去
oh
哦
Pap watch
Pap 观察观察
me I'm so
我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我,我
sorry hurry
对不起对不起,快点
up
上上
hey Mr bison make sure to keep your
嘿,野牛先生 一定要保持你的
surroundings clean from now on I will
嘿 野牛先生 确保你周围的环境从现在开始保持清洁 我会的
从今以后干净的周围环境 我会的
surroundings clean from now on I will
and I'll never litter
从今以后干净的周围环境 我将永不丢弃
again Sheriff labrador's safety talk
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话
kids mosquitoes in summer are annoying
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们在夏天的蚊子很烦人
夏天的蚊子小孩很烦人
kids mosquitoes in summer are annoying
not only do they fight but they can also
夏天的蚊子孩子很烦人 不仅他们打斗,而且他们也可以打
他们不仅战斗,而且可以战斗
not only do they fight but they can also
spread
他们不仅战斗,而且可以散布,
展开
spread
diseases mosquitoes usually breed in
蚊子通常在
dirty and wet places so we need to keep
蚊子通常在肮脏和湿湿的地方繁殖,所以我们需要保持
肮脏湿湿的地方 所以我们需要保持
dirty and wet places so we need to keep
our houses
肮脏和潮湿的地方 所以我们需要 保持我们的房子
我们的房屋
our houses
clean also we need to keep our town
我们的房屋清净,我们也需要 保持我们的小镇
还要保持城市的干净
clean also we need to keep our town
clean and don't Litter please remember
还要清干净 我们还需要保持城市的干净 并且不要放放风 请记住
清干净又不放放,请记住
clean and don't Litter please remember
that don't play with
请记住,不玩
sockets
套接插件
Go
上
Dino welcome to robot snack house how
迪诺欢迎来到机器人小吃店
can I help
迪诺,欢迎来到机器人小吃店,我能帮什么忙?
我能帮忙吗?
can I help
you I want to get some
我可以帮你吗? 我想来点
too here's your ice
你的冰冰也在这里
cream
你的冰淇淋也在这里
yay it's so
呀呀,是这么
yummy wow one chocolate cake
好好吃喔,一个巧克力蛋糕
好吃哇一个巧克力蛋糕
yummy wow one chocolate cake
please okay
好吃喔,一个巧克力蛋糕,好吗?
好,请好
please okay
please what's going on huh chocolate
拜托你,这是怎么回事啊? 巧克力吗?
chocolate
朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱的朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱的朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱朱的
huh chocolate cake is ready oh no the
巧克力蛋糕做好了哦,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
robot turned me into a cake Blueberry
巧克力蛋糕做好了 哦 没有 机器人把我变成蛋糕
机器人把我变成蛋糕 蓝莓
robot turned me into a cake Blueberry
Blueberry
机器人把我变成一个蛋糕 蓝莓蓝莓蓝莓蓝莓
蓝莓
Blueberry
help let me go blueberry ice cream is
让我去吃蓝莓冰淇淋
ready oh that's so
让我去吃蓝莓冰淇淋吧
哦,这是如此
ready oh that's so
terrible
哦,这太可怕了
可怕
terrible
ouch the juice cup needs to be filled
果汁杯要装满
with juice yummy juice is ready
果汁杯要装满果汁汁 果汁已经准备好了
果汁汁美味的果汁已经准备好了
with juice yummy juice is ready
please help H what's going
果汁汁美味果汁准备好了 请帮H什么忙
on a super
在一个超级
donut
甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜甜圈
help Miss king rat snake what made you
帮助大老鼠蛇小姐 是什么让你变成这样
become a donut Sheriff Labrador
帮助王鼠蛇小姐 是什么让你成为甜甜圈拉布拉多警长
成为甜甜圈拉布拉多警长
become a donut Sheriff Labrador
something's wrong with the robot in the
变成一个甜甜圈警长拉布拉多 机器人有问题
机器人有问题
something's wrong with the robot in the
snack house huh let's go have a look
零食店的机器人有问题 我们去看看吧
零点点小吃店,我们去看看
snack house huh let's go have a look
help us
点零点小吃小吃店 我们去帮我们看一看
please oh no they all became food hot
哦,不,请不要,他们都变热了
dog hot
哦,请不要,他们都成了热热热狗
dog ah stop chasing me Doby draw the
狗狗啊 别再追我 多比画画
robot's attention help you let's save
别再追我 多比吸引机器人的注意 帮你救救
机器人的注意帮助你 省省吧
robot's attention help you let's save
others hey robot look here
机器人的注意力帮助你 拯救其他人,嘿,机器人看这里
其它机器人看看这里
others hey robot look here
come on turn me into a hot dog hot dog
来把我变成热狗热狗热狗
把我变成热狗热狗
come on turn me into a hot dog hot dog
hot
把我变成热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热热
热热
hot
dog it's coming come on uh-oh
热狗热狗 快来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊 来啊
run we're safe
跑跑,我们安全了
now oh no it's so fast Sheriff
跑跑,我们安全了 警长,这太快了
哦,不,现在太快了,警长
now oh no it's so fast Sheriff
Labrador I can't go on I have an idea
哦,不,现在太快了 拉布拉多警长 我不能继续了 我有一个主意
拉布拉多 我不能继续下去 我有一个想法
Labrador I can't go on I have an idea
let's run circles around the
拉布拉多,我不能继续 我有一个想法,让我们绕圈圈圈
robot strawberry mango avocado proag
机器人草莓芒果
proag
约 约 纳
uh finally it
终于
stopped what's wrong with the food robot
终于停止了食物机器人的毛病
停止什么是错的 与食物机器人
stopped what's wrong with the food robot
papion give it a
停止什么是错的 食品机器人Papion给它一个
check it circuits are broken no wonder
检查电路坏了 难怪
it went out of control
检查电路断了 怪不得失控了
已经失控了
it went out of control
let's go check the
我们去查一查
shop huh the robot's charging socket is
机器人的充电插座
burnt oh no something's wrong over
机器人的充电插座被烧焦了哦 没有什么不对劲
there the sm's coming out of my house
在那里,sm's 出来 从我的房子
stay here we'll go have a
在那里,sm's从我的房子 走出我的房子 呆在这里,我们要去有一个
look huh get
长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长 长长
down
向下下下
oh my what's going
哦,我的下 发生的一切
哦,我的什么 发生
oh my what's going
on look the dino robot's hand got stuck
哦,我的什么是怎么回事 看着迪诺机器人的手被卡住了
看着迪诺机器人的手被卡住了
on look the dino robot's hand got stuck
in the socket that's what made the food
迪诺机器人的手 被卡在插座里 所以才有食物
在插座里,食物就是靠这个做成的
in the socket that's what made the food
robot and other sockets broken we need
使食物机器人 和其他插座破碎 我们需要的
机器人和其他插座都坏了 我们需要的
robot and other sockets broken we need
to turn off the
机器人和其他插座被打破 我们需要关掉
关闭
to turn off the
power over
关闭电源
there leave it to me
交给我,交给我
hey huh trash detected trash detected go
留给我吧 嘿 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾 垃圾 垃圾检测到的垃圾
哈哈哈哈哈 垃圾检测到的垃圾检测到的垃圾去
hey huh trash detected trash detected go
away I'm not
垃圾检测到的垃圾 走开,我不是
离开我,我不是
away I'm not
trash
# 我不是垃圾 # # # 我不是垃圾 # # 我不是垃圾 # # 我不是垃圾 #
垃圾垃圾垃圾
trash
huh watch your
注意安全, 注意安全, 注意安全, 特别是
back hey power
背后hey 电源
off oh that was so scary Little Bear you
哦,那太吓人了 小熊你
should stay away from sockets
哦,那太可怕了 小熊,你应该离插座远一点
离插座应该离插座远一点
should stay away from sockets
okay I got
离插座应该离插座远一点
还好,我得到了
okay I got
it Sheriff labrador's safety
是拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids sockets are very dangerous and
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们的插座非常危险
闲聊孩子的插座非常危险
talk kids sockets are very dangerous and
you should never touch them if you do
闲聊孩子的插座非常危险,如果有的话,你不应该碰它们
如果你碰过他们,就永远不要碰他们
you should never touch them if you do
you could get seriously hurt by electric
你不应该碰他们,如果你碰他们,如果你碰他们, 你可能会受到严重的 电击伤害
电能严重伤害
you could get seriously hurt by electric
shock so if you need to use electricity
电击会严重伤害您,所以如果您需要用电
如果您需要用电,请使用电
shock so if you need to use electricity
ask an adult for help please remember
如果您需要用电,请向成人请求帮助,请记住
大人求大人帮忙,请记住
ask an adult for help please remember
that little Rhino was taken by a monster
请记住 小犀牛被一个怪物带走
an
a , a , a , a , a , a
orange a
a 橙a
橙a
orange a
banana a half rotten
橙色香蕉半腐烂
香蕉半腐烂
banana a half rotten
apple wow Sheriff Labrador that was
苹果哇 拉布拉多警长 那是
awesome it was a piece of cake I even
拉布拉多警长 那真是太棒了 我甚至
棒极了,那是一块蛋糕,我什至
awesome it was a piece of cake I even
know that you haven't showered for 3
我甚至知道你3岁就没洗澡了
知道你已经3年没洗澡了
know that you haven't showered for 3
days
天天
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff Labrador
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff Labrador
little Rhino was taken by a monster
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多小犀牛被怪物抓走
小犀牛被一个怪物抓走
little Rhino was taken by a monster
please help him a monster don't worry
小犀牛被一个怪物抓走 请帮帮他一个怪物不要担心
帮帮他吧 怪物不要担心
please help him a monster don't worry
kid we'll be right
帮帮他一个怪物,别担心 孩子,我们做对了
小子,我们不会错的
kid we'll be right
there the sh labador what do you mean
在那里的拉玛朵 你什么意思?
that little Rhino was taken by a
小犀牛被一个
monster well we were playing hide and
那个小犀牛 被我们玩捉迷藏的怪物的井拿走了
我们在玩捉迷藏
monster well we were playing hide and
seek and we looked for him everywhere
我们在玩捉捉捉捉捉捉捉捉捉捉捉捉,到处找他
我们到处寻找他,我们到处寻找他,
seek and we looked for him everywhere
but couldn't find
我们到处找他,却找不到
him my grandma told me there is a
我外婆告诉我有一个
monster that only takes children who
我奶奶告诉我有个怪物 只带走那些孩子的孩子
只能带走那些
monster that only takes children who
don't take a
它只带走不带走儿童的孩子
不拿一个
don't take a
shower little Rhino's feet smell really
不要洗澡 小犀牛的脚闻起来真香
小犀牛的脚真的有香味
shower little Rhino's feet smell really
bad so it must be the monster who took
小犀牛的脚闻起来很臭 所以一定是怪物带走了
坏坏,所以一定是那个怪物带走了
bad so it must be the monster who took
him well
坏坏的,所以一定是怪物 将他很好
好,好,他
him well
kids there's no
他的孩子好好孩子 没有
monster wait little Rhino's feet smell
等待小犀牛脚的气味
bad that's an important clue if we
等待小犀牛脚的臭臭味 这是一个重要的线索,如果我们
坏坏坏是一条重要线索 如果我们
bad that's an important clue if we
follow the smell of his feet we'll be
如果我们跟着他的脚的气味 就会成为重要的线索
跟着他的脚的气味 我们将是
follow the smell of his feet we'll be
able to find him
跟着他的脚的气味 我们就能找到他了
smell
气味气味
I got
我拿到了
it it smells
闻闻闻闻闻
terrible who didn't flush the
闻起来很可怕 谁没有冲冲
可怕的人,谁没有冲冲
terrible who didn't flush the
toilet I think I smell the
我想我闻到厕所的味道
evidence
我想我闻到了证据的味道
oh come on it's just a smelly
哦,来吧,这只是一股臭味
shoe little Rhino must be hiding in
小犀牛一定躲在
here hey little Rhino don't worry I'll
小犀牛一定躲在这里 嘿 小犀牛别担心 我会的
小犀牛,别担心,我会的
here hey little Rhino don't worry I'll
get you out
嘿 小犀牛别担心 我会救你出去的
让你出去
get you out
there he
在那里的他
is little Rhino little
他有小犀牛,他有小犀牛
小犀牛是小犀牛
is little Rhino little
Rhino what
犀牛什么
happened we got you were Tak by
瑞诺,我们给你带来的一切... ...你就是德哥
发生发生我们得到你 德哥经过
happened we got you were Tak by
monster when we started playing hide and
当我们开始玩捉迷藏
seek I thought that if I hit in the
当我们开始玩捉迷藏 寻找我的想法
寻找我的想法,如果我打中
seek I thought that if I hit in the
closet you wouldn't find
找寻我的想法 如果我打在衣柜 你就不会发现
me what it was so dark and
我当时如此黑暗
stuffy I tried to get out but the door
闷闷不乐 我想出去,但门
wouldn't
我试着出去,但门不开门
open I was so
# 我当时如此开开开开开开开开开开开开开开开 # # #
scared little Rhino it's really
我当时很害怕 小犀牛 真的
小犀牛吓坏了 真的
scared little Rhino it's really
dangerous to hide in the closet never do
小犀牛害怕了 躲在衣柜里真的很危险
躲在壁橱里的危险
dangerous to hide in the closet never do
that again
躲在壁橱里的危险 永远不要再那样做了
重新显示
that again
okay I'll never do that
再说一次,好吗 好吧,我永远不会这样做
again Sheriff labrador's safety talk
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话
kids please be careful when you play
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们,请小心,当你玩
孩子们玩的时候要小心一点
kids please be careful when you play
hide and seek never hide in a closet or
孩子们玩捉迷藏时要小心 永远不要躲在壁橱里
隐居而永不躲藏在衣柜里,
hide and seek never hide in a closet or
a chest you could run out of
躲藏在衣柜中,不躲在衣柜中,也不躲藏在心胸中,你绝不能逃避,
胸口,你可以跑出
a chest you could run out of
air and don't hide in narrow places
胸口,你可以跑出空气 而不隐藏在狭窄的地方
不要躲藏在狭窄的空气中
air and don't hide in narrow places
under the sofa you could be stuck stairs
不要躲在沙发下面的狭窄地方 你可能会被卡在楼梯上
沙发下面的沙发下 你可能会被卡在楼梯上
under the sofa you could be stuck stairs
and balconies are dangerous too you
沙发下面的沙发下 你可能会被卡在楼梯上 阳台也太危险了
和阳台也是危险的,你也太危险了
and balconies are dangerous too you
could fall and get hurt remember never
和阳台是危险的太危险 你可能跌倒 受伤受伤 永远记不记得了
可能摔倒受伤 永远记不记得
could fall and get hurt remember never
hide in dangerous
记得永远不要躲在危险中
隐藏在危险之中
hide in dangerous
places don't play with
隐藏在危险的地方 不玩
地方不玩玩
places don't play with
soap hey
地方不玩肥皂,嘿嘿嘿
it's so much fun oh my look at these
这太有趣了 哦,我看看这些
little buddy
这太有趣了 哦,我看看这些小家伙
kids all
全部儿童(所有儿童)
right wash off all the mud okay
洗干净所有的泥土,好吗?
body
体体
so help help us what what's
帮助我们什么是
wrong what's going
错误的是什么正在发生
on wo hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador it's Mr elephant my house
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 这是大象先生 我的房子
拉布拉多 是大象先生 我的房子
Labrador it's Mr elephant my house
floating with bubbles we'll be right
拉布拉多,这是大象先生 我的房子漂浮
there oh my what's with all these
哦,我的什么 与所有这些
bubbles let's get
哦,我的什么 与所有这些泡泡 让我们得到
泡泡,让我们开始
bubbles let's get
inside oh where's the door
里面哦 门在哪里
oh the door knobs
哦,门把手
here that's strange the door knobs
这里的门把手怪怪的
running away H gotcha ouch my
奇怪的是,门把手 跑开的门把手
奔跑的H 得到cha 摸我的
running away H gotcha ouch my
nose I'm
鼻子,我鼻子,我鼻子
sorry come here I found the
鼻子鼻子,对不起,来这里,我发现
door
门门
bubbles Len to
Len to 门泡泡
气泡泡泡
bubbles Len to
me I'm going to blow them all
我要把他们全炸飞
away Mr elephant where are
离开大象先生 在那里
youby
以 千 以
finally Mr
最后,先生,最后先生
elephant I've got bubbles in my eyes it
大象,我眼睛里有泡泡
hurts so much bubbles can harm your eyes
大象,我眼睛里有泡泡, 痛得要命 这么多泡泡会伤你的眼睛
如此多的泡沫会伤害你的眼睛
hurts so much bubbles can harm your eyes
let's wash them up right
如此多的泡沫会伤害你的眼睛 让我们把它们洗洗干净
洗洗吧 洗洗干净吧
let's wash them up right
now what's that sound
现在就洗洗吧,那是什么声音?
现在那是什么声音?
now what's that sound
my kids are still upstairs please save
现在是什么声音 我的孩子还在楼上 请救救
我的孩子还在楼上 请救救
my kids are still upstairs please save
them little brother where are
我的孩子还在楼上 请救救他们弟弟
弟弟们,他们在哪里?
them little brother where are
you
弟弟们,你在哪里?
brother let's go
兄弟,我们走吧
upstairs
楼上
aw the floor is all slippery with
楼上的地板很滑
地板都滑滑
aw the floor is all slippery with
bubbles papion we need some slip proof
地板都滑了,泡泡泡泡泡 我们需要一些滑滑的证明
泡泡泡泡泡,我们需要一些滑滑证明
bubbles papion we need some slip proof
tools got it slip proof tool slip proof
我们需要一些滑动验证工具 得到滑动验证工具 滑动验证工具滑动验证
工具工具得到了它滑滑证明工具滑滑证明
tools got it slip proof tool slip proof
tool this will do
工具得到它滑滑验证工具滑滑验证工具
工具可以使用此工具
tool this will do
taada huh a
这个工具可以用来做塔达哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF
taada huh a
plunger they were
他们曾经是
great
伟大
help it's brother elepant
帮个大忙,这是弟弟埃利潘特
hey that was so scary
嘿,那太吓人了
help oh no watch
帮助 oh no watch 手表
out
外出
Daddy Daddy was so
爸爸爸爸是那样的
worried oh no the whole bottle is empty
爸爸很担心爸爸,哦,没有整个瓶子是空的
整个瓶子都是空的
worried oh no the whole bottle is empty
no wonder there were so many bubbles
哦,不,整个瓶子是空的 难怪有这么多泡泡
难怪有这么多的泡沫
no wonder there were so many bubbles
kids playing with body soap is very
难怪有这么多的泡泡泡泡泡 小孩玩肥皂很特别
玩体肥皂的小孩非常
kids playing with body soap is very
dangerous we'll never do that
玩肥皂的小孩很危险 我们绝不会这么做的
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids don't play with body soap hand
说闲话的小孩不玩体肥皂手
soap or shampoo which all make many
说闲话的小孩不玩 身体肥皂手肥皂或洗发水
肥皂或洗发水
soap or shampoo which all make many
bubbles if they drip on the floor you
洗发肥皂或洗发香皂,如果在地板上滴水,都会产生许多泡泡
泡泡,如果它们滴在地板上,你
bubbles if they drip on the floor you
can slip on them and get hurt and if the
如果它们滴在地上, 泡泡就会滑到地上,然后受伤,如果
可能滑倒在他们身上 并受到伤害,如果
can slip on them and get hurt and if the
bubbles get in your eyes they can make
如果泡泡在你眼里 它们就能制造出
泡泡进入你的眼睛 它们能制造
bubbles get in your eyes they can make
your eyes sting or even worse please
泡泡在你眼里 它们能让你的眼睛刺痛 或更糟
你的眼睛痛,甚至更糟 请
your eyes sting or even worse please
remember
眼眼痛或眼痛,甚至更糟 请记住
that don't go with others
不和别人一起走
pets Mommy will go get some ice cream
妈妈会去吃冰淇淋的
stay here and wait until mommy's back
妈妈会去买些冰淇淋 住在这里等妈妈回来
待在这里等妈妈回来
stay here and wait until mommy's back
okay ha this is my chance it's my pet
留在这儿等妈妈回来 好吗 这是我的机会,这是我的宠物
这可是我的机会,是我的宠物
okay ha this is my chance it's my pet
Lulu's
哈哈,这是我的机会 这是我的宠物露露的
Showtime let's get
表演时间 让我们开始吧
started wow you look so
哇,你看起来好帅啊
cute there you
哇,你看起来好可爱啊
are sir is this Lulu your pet it's so
先生,这是露露的宠物吗?
cute isn't it
先生,这是露露的宠物吗? 太可爱了,不是吗?
可爱不可爱吗?
cute isn't it
cute oh I need to go to the bathroom now
可爱不可爱吗? 哦,我现在要去洗手间
可爱哦 我现在要去洗手间了
cute oh I need to go to the bathroom now
can you watch my Lulu for me for a
哦,可爱,哦,我需要去洗手间 现在,你能帮我看看我的露露吗?
你能帮我帮我照看我的露露吗?
can you watch my Lulu for me for a
second
你能帮我看一眼我的露露吗?
okay stop don't
别停,别停,别停,别停,别停,别停
go
不要走,别走,别走
wow smells
哇闻闻闻的气味
great oh sty these are pet
闻起来好香啊,哦,斯蒂,这些是宠物
cookies but it tastes good though of
饼干虽然好吃,但味道不错
course because I made them
饼干,虽然味道很好吃,当然是因为我做的
是因为我造了它们
course because I made them
myself hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
我是拉布拉多警长 我是拉布拉多警长
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长 我是拉布拉多警长
myself hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador help me my child little sheep
嗨 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 帮助我孩子的羊
拉布拉多帮助我 我的孩子小绵羊
Labrador help me my child little sheep
is missing please come right now what
拉布拉多帮我,我的小孩 少了一只小绵羊 请马上过来
失踪了,请马上过来
is missing please come right now what
we'll be right
失踪了,请马上过来 做我们该做的对的事
there Sheriff Labrador my daughter was
拉布拉多警长 我女儿是
playing right here but she disappeared
拉布拉多警长 我女儿就在这里弹琴 但她失踪了
就在这里玩,但她失踪了
playing right here but she disappeared
in a Flash what should I
却在闪光闪光闪闪中消失 我该怎样
在一个闪光的闪光中,我怎样做呢?
in a Flash what should I
do don't worry there's no case that I
"闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪光闪光闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪光的闪光的闪光的闪光光闪光闪光闪光闪光闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪的闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪的闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪闪的闪的闪的闪的闪的闪的闪的闪
不用担心,没有案子我
do don't worry there's no case that I
can't
不要担心,没有案子我不能办
不能
can't
solve Doby let's investigate the
解决多比的问题,让我们来调查
scene not here not here
不在现场, 不在现场
either these are little sheep's
要么这些是小绵羊的
Footprints what's
要么这些是小绵羊的脚印
脚印
Footprints what's
this I think it's a red Lulu's hair
脚印,这是什么 我觉得是红露露的头发
我觉得是红露露的头发
this I think it's a red Lulu's hair
according to the footprints little sheep
我想这是根红色露露的头发 根据脚脚脚小绵羊的脚印
根据脚足足迹,小绵羊
according to the footprints little sheep
and the Lulu went that way if we find
根据脚脚足足迹 小绵羊和露露 走走的路 如果我们发现
露露去了那条路 如果我们发现
and the Lulu went that way if we find
the Lulu we will find Little Sheep
如果我们找到露露 我们就会找到小羊
露露 我们会找到小羊
the Lulu we will find Little Sheep
aha woof this is papion papion we need
露露 我们会找到小羊羊 和哈 呜呼 这是papion papion 我们需要的papion
这才是我们需要的Papion papion
aha woof this is papion papion we need
your pet cookies the more the better no
这是Papion papion 我们需要你的宠物饼干 越多越好
你的宠物饼干越多越好
your pet cookies the more the better no
problem little mon
小问题小问题
time take these cookies to
小时间问题 小时间 把这些饼干
them we'll be able to find the red Lulu
我们就能找到红色露露
with these cookies do you you think it
他们能用这些饼干找到红色露露 你觉得呢?
这些饼干,你觉得呢?
with these cookies do you you think it
will
用这些饼干,你认为它会吗?
work this is way too good there isn't
工作干得太好了,没有
any red Lulu
工作干得太好了,没有红露露
任何红色露露
any red Lulu
here let's
任何红色露露露在这里,让我们
go stay away for
离我远走远去
me don't run I can't keep up with
我跑不跑,我跟不上
you where am
我跑不跑,我跟不上你,你在哪里?
地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点 地点
you where am
I hm
你在哪里,我,嗯
我... 我... 我...
I hm
good
嗯,嗯,我很好
良好
good
job oh where are you come out please
好工作哦,你在哪里 出来,请
工作哦,你在哪里出来 请出来,请
job oh where are you come out please
huh I got you
工作啊 工作啊 工作啊 工作啊 你到哪儿了 出来啊
hi these are all the cookies we
嗨,这些都是所有的饼干,我们
got another
获得另一个
Lulu red
得到了另一个露露红色
露露红色
Lulu red
hair the same Footprints that's it
露露红发 同样的脚印 就是这样
同样的脚印
hair the same Footprints that's it
follow
同样的脚印
续 续
follow
it where's my
顺着它,我的
# 在那里是我的爱 # # # 在那里是我的爱 # # # #
it where's my
Lulu there you
哪里是我的露露,你在那里
露露,你在那里
Lulu there you
are hey
露露,你在这里呀
police Labrador you're safe now stop you
警察拉布拉多 你现在安全了 阻止你
can't get
警察拉布拉多,你现在安全了 停止,你不能得到
买不到
can't get
away
跑不掉的跑不开
really
真的
I'll go first see you
真的,我先去见你
我先去见你
I'll go first see you
later watch
晚点我先去看你
me nobody can run away from
没有人能逃离我
me Sheriff labrador's safety
我是拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids pets may look cute but you
闲聊小孩的宠物 可能看起来可爱,但你
need to be careful because bad people
闲聊孩子的宠物可能看起来很可爱 但你需要小心 因为坏人
需要小心小心 因为坏人
need to be careful because bad people
people might use them to trick you if a
需要小心小心 因为坏人可能会利用他们来欺骗你
人们可能会利用它们来欺骗你,如果
people might use them to trick you if a
stranger asks you to take care of a pet
如果陌生人要你照顾宠物 别人可能会用它们来骗你
陌生人叫你照顾宠物
stranger asks you to take care of a pet
or to come home with them to see other
陌生人要你照顾宠物 或者和他们一起回家看别人
或回家去见别的人,
or to come home with them to see other
pets they have don't listen to them
或者和他们一起回家看他们所不倾听的其他宠物。
他们不听从的宠物
pets they have don't listen to them
please remember
他们没听宠物的宠物 请记住
请记住,请记住
please remember
that falling
请记住,坠落
firecrackers oh no I've got to
哦,不,我必须
go
上去
R Sheriff Labrador someone Just Dropped
拉布拉多警长 有人刚丢下
a Bomb into the restroom what a bomb yes
拉布拉多警长 有人刚把炸弹扔进洗手间
炸弹进入洗手间... 炸弹是...
a Bomb into the restroom what a bomb yes
and I got burned please find doubt who
一个炸弹进入厕所... ...一个炸弹... ...是的,我被烧了...
我被烧了,请怀疑是谁
and I got burned please find doubt who
did this don't
我被烧了,请怀疑是谁干的
做这个不是做这个的
did this don't
worry there's no case that I can't
做这个不用担心 没有案子我办不到
solve I can't see any traces of the bomb
我看不到炸弹的痕迹
what's
我看不到任何炸弹的痕迹
什么是
what's
that
这是什么
,该数额,
that
huh it's just a
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE、
firecracker the firecracker must have
鞭炮必须有 鞭炮的鞭炮
come through the vent over there but the
火炮一定是从通风口穿过 那边的排气口,但是...
穿过那边的通风口,但是...
come through the vent over there but the
vent is so high up on the
通过那边的通风口 但通风口高高在上
排气孔太高了
vent is so high up on the
wall who could have done
他们本可以造墙的,
it over
翻过它
there let's
在那边,我们到那边去
在那里,让我们
there let's
go my sand castle is ruined
我的沙沙城堡被毁了
my ice
我的冰冰
cream oh man why can't we even see the
哦,男人啊,为什么我们甚至看不到
suspect firecrackers
为什么我们连疑凶的鞭炮都看不到呢?
again sure Labrador we were taking
再次确定拉布拉多 我们正采取
pictures here and suddenly a firecracker
再一次肯定拉布拉多 我们在这里拍照 突然一个鞭炮手
这里的图片 突然间一个鞭炮
pictures here and suddenly a firecracker
flew towards us it's
突然一个鞭炮向着我们飞过来
terrible taking pictures can I see the
拍摄可怕的照片 我能看看吗?
pictures please
拍些可怕的照片 我能看看那些照片吗?
请显示图片
pictures please
mhm
小时
look here's the
看这里
suspect it can fly that's why we
所以,我们才怀疑它会飞
couldn't find it
所以我们找不到它
找不到它
couldn't find it
ouch oh I'm sorry I didn't see you
找不到,对不起,没看见你
啊,哦,对不起,我没看见你
ouch oh I'm sorry I didn't see you
coming what are you looking at
对不起,我没想到你来了 你在看什么
there I'm not looking at anything I'm
在那里,我没有在看 任何东西,我
keeping my head up because my neck is
我没在看什么,我保持我的头 抬起我的头,因为我的脖子是
我的头抬高,因为我的脖子
keeping my head up because my neck is
hurt Mr giraffe did you see anyone
因为我的脖子受伤了 长颈鹿先生 你有没有看到任何人
长颈鹿先生受伤 你有没有看到任何人
hurt Mr giraffe did you see anyone
flying
长颈鹿先生受伤 你看到有人飞过吗?
飞行飞行
flying
around let's see Two Sparrows a pigeon
飞来飞来飞去 让我们看看"双雀雀"一只鸽子
让我们看看两麻雀一只鸽子
around let's see Two Sparrows a pigeon
and a flying
让我们看看两麻雀 一只鸽子和飞翔的鸽子
和飞飞的,
and a flying
squirrel a fly fing
飞的松鼠飞翔 飞的松鼠飞翔
squirrel the suspect is probably the
疑犯可能是松松鼠
Flying Squirrel which way did he fly huh
松鼠 疑犯可能是飞松鼠 飞松鼠
松鼠飞哪条路? 他飞哪条路?
Flying Squirrel which way did he fly huh
that
松鼠飞哪条路? 他飞哪条路?
way wow firecrackers are so much
哇哇 鞭炮是如此多
fun 1 2 1 2 1 2 1
哇哇 鞭炮是这么多的乐趣 12,12,12,12,1
2 here's a big one for
2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个大,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个,2个
you 1 2 2 1 2 1 2 1
一、二、二、一、二、二、一、二、二、二、二、一
2 what's going
发生2件事情
on I'm on
我上
fire
火灾
help oh there
点火帮助哦
hurry
快点
that was so
是这样
scary little flying squirrel you should
刚才那小飞飞的松鼠真吓人
可怕的飞飞小松鼠 你应该
scary little flying squirrel you should
never play tricks on others with
可怕的飞飞小松鼠 你不应该和别人玩把戏
永远不要和别人玩把戏
never play tricks on others with
firecrackers you could hurt other people
永远不要用鞭炮对别人耍花招 你可能会伤害别人
你可以伤害别人的鞭炮
firecrackers you could hurt other people
and yourself
你可能会伤害别人和你自己
和你自己
and yourself
too I'm so sorry sheriff
和你自己也一样 对不起警长
Labrador Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多郡长拉布拉多的安全
talk kids firecrackers are
说闲话的小孩 鞭炮是
dangerous you should never light them
闲聊小孩的鞭炮很危险 千万不要点火
危险,你不该点燃它们
dangerous you should never light them
without
危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险 危险
无
without
permission if your parents say it's okay
如果你父母说可以的话 未经允许
如果你父母说可以的话,可以
permission if your parents say it's okay
make sure to have them by your side and
如果你父母说可以的话 一定要让他们在你身边
确保他们在你身边
make sure to have them by your side and
be careful please remember to do
一定要让他们在你身边 小心点,请记住
一定要小心,请记住要小心
be careful please remember to do
that baby swan got
一定要小心,请记住 做婴儿天鹅得到的。
那个小天鹅
that baby swan got
lost oh Mommy
那个婴儿天鹅迷路了 哦,妈妈
失失的妈妈
lost oh Mommy
Mommy
失去的妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈
ouch
触摸( A)
hey little kid are you all
嘿,小孩子,你们都是
right I lost my
右右,我失去了我的
mommy don't cry kid we'll help you find
妈妈别哭,孩子,我们帮你找
your mommy don't worry there's no case
妈妈别哭,孩子,我们帮你找妈妈 不要担心没有案子
你妈妈不用担心 没有案子
your mommy don't worry there's no case
that I can't
你妈妈不用担心 没有案子我不能办
solve kid what's your name
解答孩子你叫什么名字
my name is gray and your mommy's name
解决孩子 你叫什么名字 我叫灰色 你妈妈的名字
我的名字是灰灰的 你妈妈的名字
my name is gray and your mommy's name
mommy um I mean what's your mommy's
我的名字是灰色的 你妈妈的名字是妈妈 嗯 我是说什么是你妈妈的名字
妈妈 嗯 我是说什么是你妈妈的
mommy um I mean what's your mommy's
name it's just
妈咪 嗯 我是说你妈妈叫什么名字 只是...
它只是名字
name it's just
mommy well do you know your mommy's
妈妈,你知道你妈妈的吗?
phone number oh maybe
妈妈,你知道你妈妈的电话号码吗? 哦,也许
电话号码哦,也许
phone number oh maybe
7773 and
电话号码: oh maybe 7773 and
three
3个 3
hello
3个哈哈哈哈 3个哈哈哈 3个哈哈
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
hello
hello are you Gray's
你好 你好 你好 你是灰色的吗
你好,你们好,格雷的
hello are you Gray's
mommy
你好 格雷的妈妈
妈妈
mommy
what gray gr
妈妈什么灰色的灰色
what
什么什么是
gr as my gray skirt
穿成我的灰色裙子
arrived it's nothing
当我的白裙子穿成灰色时
到了就没什么事啦
arrived it's nothing
sorry hey gray are you sure it's
已经到了,没什么可抱歉的,嘿嘿,灰色 你确定是的
对不起,嘿,灰灰色 你确定它是
sorry hey gray are you sure it's
77733 uh I don't remember then do you
对不起,嘿嘿,灰灰色 你确定这是777733 嗯,我不记得了,那你还记得吗?
777733 uh 我不记得了 那你呢?
77733 uh I don't remember then do you
know your address um no I just know
77733 uh 我不记得了 你知道你的地址吗 嗯 不 我只是知道
知道你的地址 嗯 不 我只是知道
know your address um no I just know
there's a big pond by my house a pond
我知道我家旁边有个大池塘 一个池塘
我家旁边有一个大池塘 一个池塘
there's a big pond by my house a pond
the wild goose family live by the pond
我家边有个大池塘 池塘 野鹅家族住在池塘边
野鹅家庭住在池塘旁
the wild goose family live by the pond
great let's go to their
野鹅家庭住在池塘旁 伟大的,让我们去他们的
好极了,让我们去他们的
great let's go to their
house how is it
房子是怎么样的?
Sheriff Labrador can I help you Mr wild
拉布拉多警长 有什么我能帮你的吗 野人先生
goose are all of your children home
拉布拉多警长,我能帮你吗? 野鹅先生都是你的孩子
你所有的孩子都在家吗?
goose are all of your children home
right now of course they're all at home
鹅是所有你的孩子 现在回家,现在 他们当然都在家里
现在他们当然都在家
right now of course they're all at home
with me everyone gather
现在,他们当然都在家 和我在一起,大家集合
up 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 a I have only six
12 3 4 5 5 6 7 a 我只有6个
children
12 3 4 5 5 6 7 a 我只有六个孩子
儿 儿 儿 儿 儿
children
why are there seven
为什么有七个孩子?
Now where's
现在在哪里
gray which one is
哪里是灰色 哪里是灰色
灰色是
gray which one is
gray
灰色哪一个是灰色
灰色
gray
aha everyone line
灰原每条线
upow wait
等待等待等待
aha I got you
等待等待啊哈,我得到了你
gray we haven't found any
灰色,我们没有找到任何
clue huh Mumu ice cream I love mumo ice
灰色,我们没有找到任何线索 穆木冰淇淋,我爱木木木冰
我爱木木冰 我爱木木木冰 我爱木木木冰
clue huh Mumu ice cream I love mumo ice
cream gray do you and your mommy often
我爱木木木儿 我爱木木木儿 我爱木木木木儿 你和你妈妈经常去吗?
奶油灰色 你和你妈妈经常
cream gray do you and your mommy often
come here to buy Mumu ice cream
你和你妈妈经常来这里买薄荷冰淇淋吗?
来买薄荷冰淇淋
come here to buy Mumu ice cream
uh-huh then let's go and
来买薄荷冰淇淋
嗯,然后让我们去
uh-huh then let's go and
ask hi may I help you is C do you know
问你好,我可以帮你忙吗? 是C,你知不知道?
gray here gray what are you doing here
问您好,请问您能帮您C吗? 您知道这里灰灰灰吗? 你在这里做什么?
灰灰灰灰的这里 你在这里做什么
gray here gray what are you doing here
your mommy was looking for
灰灰灰灰的这里 你在这里做什么 你妈妈一直在寻找
你妈妈在找
your mommy was looking for
you where did she go that
你妈妈找你,她去哪里了?
way huh
经济、社会、经济、社会、
Mommy a swine so gray is a little
这么灰色的猪妈妈 有点灰色
妈妈 一只灰色的猪 有点
Mommy a swine so gray is a little
swine mommy
母猪 灰色的猪 是一只小猪 母猪
mommy mommy is
妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈
missing she's over
妈妈妈妈不见了,妈妈不见了,她已经结束了
失踪的她已经结束了
missing she's over
there where's my
失踪了,她就在那边 哪里是我的
child coming through sorry excuse
以令人遗憾的借口入境的儿童
me we can't catch up with her what do we
对不起,我们追不上她 我们该怎么办?
do I have an
我有一个
idea yeah Miss Swan Miss Sheriff
斯旺小姐 警长小姐
laborator finally look over there
总之 Swan小姐 Swan小姐 Swan小姐 警长小姐 警长女士
劳工总算看那边了
laborator finally look over there
Mommy
妈咪妈妈妈妈
Mommy Mommy Mommy oh
妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈哦
sweetie oh where did you go my child oh
妈妈妈妈妈妈哦亲爱的哦 你去哪了 我的孩子哦
甜心 哦 你去哪儿了 我的孩子 哦
sweetie oh where did you go my child oh
I've been so worried about
哦,亲爱的,哦,你去哪里了 我的孩子哦,我一直如此担心
you Sheriff labrador's safety
你们是拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids when you go out with your
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们当你和你的
当你和孩子约会时 和孩子聊天的时候
talk kids when you go out with your
parents you should always stay close to
当你和父母约会时 和孩子聊天的时候 你总是应该跟在身边
父母亲应始终与父母亲保持密切的距离。
parents you should always stay close to
them and if you lose them stay where you
父母应始终与父母亲保持亲密关系,失去父母的父母应留在原地
如果你失去他们 留在原地
them and if you lose them stay where you
are and wait for them or ask a police
如果你失去他们,请留在原地,等待他们,或问警察。
等待他们,或询问警察,
are and wait for them or ask a police
officer for help also make sure to
并且等待他们,或要求警察提供帮助,同时也确保
负责帮助的军官也确保
officer for help also make sure to
memorize your parents' phone numbers and
警官的帮助 也确保记住 你父母的电话号码 和
记得你父母的电话号码
memorize your parents' phone numbers and
your home address it will help police
记得你父母的电话号码 和你的家住址 帮警察办案
您的家住地址会帮助警察
your home address it will help police
officers find your parents please keep
您的家住地址会帮助警察 找到你父母 请留下
警官 找到你父母 请留下
officers find your parents please keep
these in
警官发现你的父母 请把这些留在
中
these in
mind
所铭记的这些
本字幕由AI大模型生成